yibbida.com 2010-11-30

# Yibbida Autosurf - Privacy Statement

**Yibbida** takes great steps to keep your personal information confidential. We will not disclose your personal information outside of yibbida and its controlled subsidiaries without your consent. 

Your consent may be implied or expressed and it may also be verbal or written.  
Privacy law requires us to collect personal information about you only from you if it is reasonable and practical to do so.

Generally, you have no obligation to provide any information requested by us. However If you choose to withhold requested information, We may not be able to provide you with the goods and services that depend on the collection of that information, particularly if the collection of that information is required by law.

Yibbida recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of children. Yibbida will endeavor not to collect, use or disclose personal information about anyone under the age of 18 unless we have the consent of a parent or legal guardian. 

The personal information that we gather is generally used to provide goods or services to you. For example, for a competition we need your contact details so we can contact you if you win. We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to:   

  * Comply with the law or legal process served on Yibbida.
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of Yibbida (including the enforcement of our agreements).
  * Act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Yibbida products / services or members of the public.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, Account Information and information on technical service issues, and security announcements. We may also occasionally send you product surveys, promotional mailings or newsletters that you choose to receive. You have the right to tell us that you do not want us to send information to you other than for the main purpose for which we have collected your personal details. 

Also, from time to time, we may use external companies to provide us with detailed aggregate statistical analysis of our website traffic. 

At no time is any personal information made available to these companies, nor is the aggregate information ever merged with personal information such as your name, address, email address or other information you would consider sensitive or would compromise your privacy.

How is Personal Information Collected: Search terms that you enter when using our search engine are may be collected, but are not associated with any other information that we collect. We use these search terms for the purpose of aggregated statistical analysis so we can ascertain what people are looking for on our web site, and to improve the services that we provide.  

Yibbida, takes reasonable steps to ensure the personal information we collect, use is accurate, complete and up-to-date.

If we have accurate personal information about you, it enables us to provide you with the best possible service. If you feel that the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date, please contact us immediately and we will take reasonable steps to ensure it is corrected. Where Yibbida does not agree with your view about the accuracy of the information and if you ask us to do so, we will take reasonable steps to note your claim where that information is stored and accessed

We reserve the right to make changes to the Yibbida Privacy Statement and this Privacy Policy from time to time or as required by law.

We believe that our Privacy Policy complies with the requirements of the Australian Privacy Act 1988.  

Yibbida.com
